[Music]
[Música]
On another note,
en otro orden de cosas ha pasado una
something happened yesterday that we didn't talk about. We were
cosa ayer de la que no hablamos
busy with other topics and we didn't talk,
estuvimos con otros temas y no hablamos
and what are we going to talk about then? Pilar will
y de qué vamos a hablar entonces pilar
always be there, don't worry Pilar, the
siempre habrá no te preocupes pilar las
celebrity magazines continue, Sálvame, they're
revistas del corazón siguen sálvame
not going to close it down, even to make a
tampoco lo van a cerrar hasta para pegar
fall, but sometimes it
una caída pero a veces raro no yo creo
's strange, no, I think that one day what will happen with Sálvame will be that they reinvented another program, reinvent another program, maybe with other producers, change of presenters, change of some collaborators, you know, reinvent the program, since It's already 8 o'clock, it's going very well. Yesterday in Dénia It's already 8, it had an 11, which
ayer en dénia son las 8 tuvo un 11 que
in that time slot they're very good, they've
en esa franja horaria están muy bien han
improved a lot by putting It's already 8 o'clock,
mejorado mucho poniendo el ya son las 8
okay, it's just that there's less to download it,
vale es que salva menos para descargarla
okay, yesterday there was something that we didn't talk about and that
vale ayer una cosa que no hablamos y que
went very viral, it
fue muy viral
the new addition
la nueva incorporación
of the new collaborator of 'Sálvame'
de la nueva colaboradora de 'sálvame'
but not here, do you think if instead of
pero no aquí te parece si en lugar de
doing it from this throne like today
hacerlo desde este trono así de hoy
because you came to visit, you
porque has venido de visita te
join the Sálvame team when right
incorporas al equipo de sálvame cuando
now, if I don't know what it
ya ahora mismo si yo no sé en qué
consists of, elaborated, it matters, I think  that
consiste elaborado importa ya creo que
nobody knows if it's true,
tampoco ninguno sabe si es verdad
I'm going for a loving bombardment and all
yo me animo un bombardeo cariñosa y todo
because because Samantha is poor,
porque porque es pobre
right, okay, she has become
samantha justo vale se ha convertido en
an icon of progressivism, Valley of the
un icono del progresismo valley de los
Allies has
aliados
become an
se ha convertido en un
icon, look here with Gabriel Rufián and
icono mira aquí con gabriel rufián y
here the speech, check, God,
aquí el discurso cheque dios
this was incredible at the awards, but
esto fue increíble en los premios pero
this was incredible, I think this same one, I think this same one
esto fue increíble creo que este mismo
was when I'm a
creo que esto mismo fue cuando soy una
toast, she also went there to make
brindada también fue ahí a hacer chistes
ethane jokes and things like that, not the left, the
de etano y cosas así no la izquierda la
left that we have right now in
izquierda que tenemos ahora mismo en
our country, well, it's becoming
nuestro país pues se está convirtiendo
this, okay, and because look how much it
en esto vale y porque mira cuánto
fractures, you don't know it, okay,
fracture ustedes no lo conocéis vale
but on YouTube, where he's dedicated to messing
pero en youtube que se dedica a meterse
with other YouTubers who have been
con lujo con otros youtube a los que le
bullied, and for joining
han hecho bullying y el por apuntarse a
the trend and scratching fame, well, yes, but
la moda y rascar famita pues sí pero
this is what happens with progressivism, it doesn't
esto es lo que pasa con el progresismo
matter what he does, it doesn't matter what it
es da igual lo que haga da igual lo que
is, it doesn't matter what you are, okay, if you're from the
sea da igual cómo seas vale si eres de
extreme left,
extrema izquierda
if you're from the extreme left and super
si eres de extrema izquierda y súper
progressive, and from the dahlias, they're going to call you
progre y de las dalias te van a llamar
for Netflix, okay, look at Netflix and
para netflix vales mira netflix i
collaborating with Netflix, okay, glamour
colaborando con netflix vale glamour
Spain, I'm going to  I teach the
españa ya lo voy a enseñar yo a las
pearls not of this new collaborator of
perlas no de esta nueva colaboradora de
sálvame also pointed out the pearls of
sálvame también señaló las perlitas de
this new collaborator of 'sálvame' from just now
esta nueva colaboradora de 'sálvame' de
is from a little while ago because okay
hace nada es de hace poquito porque vale
look there
mira
was also a stir on
hubo revuelo también en televisión
Spanish television because he collaborated with
española porque él colaboró con
Spanish television which is our
televisión española que es nuestra
public channel and as he came out later they
cadena pública y como salía después
also invited him he ended up
también le invitaron acabó de pasarle la
licked my little cousin's vagina
lengua a mi prima pequeña por su vagina
and he smiled at me the little ones
y me ha sonreído los más pequeños
also deserve pleasure
también merecen placer
the txupin or my [ __ ] mother makes me
el txupin o de mi [__] madre me la pone
super hard I
super dura
hate women who are victims of
odio a las mujeres que son víctimas de
rape and who turn to
violación y que recurren a centros de
self-help centers to overcome their trauma what
autoayuda para superar su trauma qué
annoying [ __ ]
[__] pesadas
if a minor came to me to ask for
si una menor de edad me viniera a pedir
help because you are being a victim of
ayuda porque estás siendo víctima de
sexual harassment I would spit in her face I
acoso sexual le escupiría en la cara
cry with laughter with videos of bullying
lloro de risa con vídeos de acoso
that ends in suicide
escolar que acaba en suicidio
pee that goes down stuffed and they let you in
pipí que baje embutida y te dejan entrar
for being a [ __ ] buy yourself a decent chin
por [__] cómprate una barbilla decente
psuv
psuv
and well they are twitter 2015 I did not
y bueno son son twitter el 2015 no lo
write it in 2015 to make of the time
escribí en 2015 para hacer de la época
even this the sailor fabric even
incluso este la tela marinera incluso
for the time okay okay we had
para la época vale vale que teníamos
things not to say it's true that in 2015
cosas no decir que es verdad que el 2015
still 2017 there were some people
todavía 2017 habíamos algunas personas
who were more brutal more sexist some
que eran más brutos más machistas algún
racist joke some joke about fat
chiste racista algún chiste sobre gordo
okay well but made too much even
vale bueno pero hecho demasiado incluso
for the time okay with new
para la época vale con nueva
collaborator of Sálvame because because it is
colaboradora de sálvame porque porque es
progressive
progre
but nothing happens the family is an ally
pero no pasa nada la familia es aliada
efe you came is an lgbt icon and they said
efe viniste es un icono lgtb y dijeron
yesterday on Sálvame you will see look
ayer en sálvame veras
samantha gusto is a singer model
samantha gusto es cantante modelo
star of televisa television star she
estrella de televisa estrella de
is this day of television and
televisión es este día de televisión y
an avant-garde innovative woman
una mujer vanguardista innovadora
reference the gp okay she is a reference
referente el gp vale es un referente
for the left now she is a reference that's it
para la izquierda ahora es un referente
because she came out of nothing happens
ya está porque salía de no pasa nada
they can say these things
ellos pueden decir estas cosas
to others they show videos from 30 years ago
a otros les sacan vídeos de hace 30 años
that are neither the nor 10 of that
que no son ni la ni el 10 de eso
and 10% of that
y el 10% de eso
but it is as if it is progressive well then we
pero está como es progre bueno pues
give you a couple of
vamos te damos un par de programas de
television programs and this is forgiven that is
televisión y esta es perdonada
the society of the left
así es la sociedad de la izquierda de
today okay that is how in society
hoy en día vale así en la sociedad hoy
today well that is not how society is
en día bueno así no es la sociedad por
luckily if they are these people  that's
suerte si son esta gente
how these people are, okay,
así es esta gente vale
incredible, new collaborator of Sálvame,
increíble nueva colaboradora de sálvame
incredible, here they whitewash whoever they want, they
increíble aquí blanquean a quien quiere
put others on an altar, they
a otros lo ponen en un altar a otros los
trample others, they
pisotean
depend on this interview was recently, she
dependen esta entrevista fue hace poco
is interviewing 2015, this is
está entrevistando a 2015 esto es hace
recently, she stated that belching and so on in
poco ha afirmado que eructar y as en la
Isabel Díaz's face is useless because to
cara de isabel díaz hay uso porque al
Caesar what belongs to Caesar and
cesar lo que es del césar y a la basura
to the garbage, well, more filth, what don't you like about her, I don't like the absolute, it's a Spanish tropism, she doesn't have a logical or well-founded proposal, she limits herself to saying populist and sensationalist things and making a speech that's worth everything in the world, she
discurso de cal en todo el mundo
really is a genius at playing
realmente es una genia en hacerse la
dumb, she plays with that vulgar attitude
tonta juega con esa actitud chabacana
dmm even as a friend she says things like about
dmm incluso de amiga dice cosas como lo
having a beer or about not
de tomarse una caña o lo de no
meeting up with your time and she's
encontrarse con tu vez y está
getting what she wants, her law is that
consiguiendo lo que quiere su ley es la
of the jungle, whoever has money is
de la jungla el que tenga dinero
phenomenal and whoever doesn't, because they rot
fenomenal y el que no porque se pudra
ah
ah
feminism
feminismo
m of woman
m de mujer
[Music]
[Música]